IBT0035
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Safety and Health Department records
2009-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0035
0.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains materials relating to the Safety and Health Department of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The material includes manuals to instruct and supplement health and safety courses. The materials range from 2009 - 2010.
Arrangement
Organized into 1 series
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials relating to the Safety and Health Department of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The material includes manuals to instruct and supplement health and safety courses. The materials range from 2009 - 2010.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters
Industrial safety; Safety of workers; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 21st century
- 10-hour OSHA Construction Safety and Health Outreach Course, 2009; series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 10-hour OSHA Construction Safety and Health Outreach Course, 2010; series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Radiological Worker II Course, 2010; series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- IBT Safety and Health Department Brochures, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Award for Outstanding Contribution to Street and Highway Safety, Orville Owings, 1964; IBT0035 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 9)
- Pfizer Legislative Conference Card, Debra Vereen, 2002; IBT0035 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 10)
- 2016 National Conference on Worker Safety & Health [flyer], IBT0035 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 9)
- Opioids can be poison, Undated; IBT0035 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 10)
- Safety and Health Courses, Undated; IBT0035 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 11)
- Safety & Health Facts, Undated; IBT0035 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 12)